<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>project on Mariia Tikhomirova, UX writer</title>
    <link>https://marykka.github.io/categories/project/</link>
    <description>Recent content in project on Mariia Tikhomirova, UX writer</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 01 May 2021 11:21:51 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://marykka.github.io/categories/project/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>intrfc lab</title>
      <link>https://marykka.github.io/posts/2021-05-01-intrfclab/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 May 2021 11:21:51 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://marykka.github.io/posts/2021-05-01-intrfclab/</guid>
      <description>As a cofounder of the project I gathered a remote team and lead the content design part; create information architecture as long as write deliverables; conduct simple user researches and Figma prototypes.
Project, context, team intrfc lab is a design collaboration. All team members work remotely. Tools: Google Docs, Figma, Affinity Designer, Notion.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>iola.app</title>
      <link>https://marykka.github.io/posts/2020-02-07-iola/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2020 11:21:51 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://marykka.github.io/posts/2020-02-07-iola/</guid>
      <description>Working for a startup as a lead UX writer, I created content architecture and wrote lots of deliverables, analyzed startup&amp;rsquo;s business rivals and all I could get about users.
Project, context, team iola.app was created as an alternative to a long and expensive mobile development. It is a plugin for websites, built on the Oxwall platform. The idea was simple: installing one mobile application iola, users could communicate with the website&amp;rsquo;s owner or with their friends from other websites, which have the iola plugin connected.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>pythagor</title>
      <link>https://marykka.github.io/posts/2019-08-01-pythagor/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2019 08:21:51 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://marykka.github.io/posts/2019-08-01-pythagor/</guid>
      <description>As a writer and UX writer of a product on the pre-alpha stage of development, I came up with ideas for the name and tone of voice, talked to dozens of possible users and wrote many different deliverables.
Project, context, team Pythagor was supposed to be a service for automatic boosting Facebook and Instagram ads, an easy and effective way for entrepreneurs and businesses to improve their Facebook and Instagram advertising.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Atlas Biomed</title>
      <link>https://marykka.github.io/posts/2019-07-01-atlas/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2019 09:11:51 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://marykka.github.io/posts/2019-07-01-atlas/</guid>
      <description>Interviewed neuroendocrinologist, cardiologist, gastroenterologists, geneticists; analyzed scientific papers and studies; translated from Russian to English and vice versa. Together with a team created a project that was presented on Yandex Conference.
Project, context, team Atlas Biomed is a personalised health company. Atlas combines DNA and microbiome technologies with digital health data to inspire people into positive lifestyle change and lead them to a healthier future. The company pays special attention to the education of its audience.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
